Thanks to our super romantical class trip?
Oh, Tani!
Tani and I are closer than we've ever been before!
You recharged your batteries after the trip?
Yeah. How are you, Suzuki?
Just kidding. Things are the same as always.
Huh? What is it? Is something wrong?
Still plain old Suzuki.
Mew.
Wait a second, but you just called me Tani instead of Yusuke.
Really? I didn't notice.
Then again, we are at school, so gotta keep things a little profesh.
Yeah, you're right.
Wait, so you wouldn't be profesh if we were, you know, alone?
You know, are you saying that if the mood was just right, you, you know?
No, I really don't think I do.
To the common eyes, this romance has made few large developments.
But the improvements are incremental.
Who are you talking to?
I'm just out here chronicling small imperfections alive.
It's got wabi-sabi.
Sato, your handwriting.
Pretty, right?
How come you're the one acting proud?
Yeah, wait a sec.
Am I crazy, or did Azuma totally shake her storm cloud?
Where's her negative aura?
Hey, Tani, did you already order some class trip pics?
Not yet.
Tani's social circle is growing.
Oh, no.
It's like whenever I take my eyes off him, he's made a new friend.
You at least have to order this one.
You're mocking us all.
I don't know what that means, but it sounds like a lie.
Susuke staring into my soul.
Show me my man's glamour shots or else.
What the heck's going on here?
Some guy walked in and we asked him to take a pic for us.
And here's the hot one.
This is so dumb.
Aw, if you won't order these, I totally will.
You should save your money.
There's so many to choose from.
You should just pick out a few faves.
These prices are highway robbery.
This reminds me of when Capacho ordered a bunch of photos from our middle school trip,
and not a single one of them had him in it.
Apparently his folks were super pissed off about it.
So we just got the landscapes?
Capacho's an artiste.
I do the same.
Boom.
Bottom.
I'm not in too many, so that was easy.
What?
There's a lot of you.
See?
You know better than to fall for deepfakes, girl!
Finally a day where I'm not bogged down by student council work.
Ever since our classmates picked me to be class rep while I was out sick,
I've hated their guts.
That being said, don't you think the class trip was super sweet?
Uh, yeah, it was nice.
Huh?
So, have you two set up your date?
What?
Uh, uh, um...
眼鏡を外してさあちゃんと目を合わせてよ
カメラのシャッターを切って恋を閉じ込めてよ
山あり谷有の恋です三角に口を尖らして四角い言葉の角取って君にハートを送りたい
I want to share my heart with my heart.
Sin, cosine, tangent.
The heart of my heart is wide open.
The power of my heart is running.
I can't remember it.
I'm feeling it.
言葉を尽くして君に伝えたいの
心が体に追いついて
気付けば目で追ってる
眼鏡を外してさ
ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出したの
放課後まで待てない
大事な言葉ほど
酸素を切らみたい
自称にない私なりの言葉で
早く
君に伝えなきゃね
I've never since mom said that I've been embarrassed to wear this stuff
I've barely ever worn this dress
Should I wear it now?
Will it be okay?
Or is it too weird for a casual meetup?
I'm usually a function over fashion kind of girl
You should always wear what you want to
It doesn't matter what people think
If you want to be a cupcake, lay on the frosting
All right, fancy dress it is
This is my chance
I've bought lots of random accessories over the years, but I've never actually worn them.
Huh?
What's going on?
What is this feeling?
My heart is racing!
And it just won't stop!
I'm heading out!
What? This early?
That was close.
I managed to leave without my family seeing me!
I'm probably realizing a little late, but nothing in my outfit actually goes well together.
I bought each item because it was cute on its own and didn't even think about coordinating it with the rest of my wardrobe.
It's funny.
I never really noticed it before today.
But all the girls walking down the street look so fashionable!
I've got to take these off!
Um, I'm already here, too.
I'm near the top of the back escalator over on the platform.
Hello! Nishi! You good? Are you lost?
No, I'm already here.
Whoa! Where at?
Um, if you go up the escalator, there's, uh, I suppose it's a plaza?
Hmm.
She'll never see me like that.
I'm standing next to the ticket gates.
Yeah.
What?
Reception isn't so...
Frickin' laser!
So formal.
And intense.
Oh, I apologize. I didn't realize it was you.
You sounded all shaky on the phone, too.
Sorry.
Wait, are you nervous?
Are you really husky cats?
Oh, yeah.
Like, you know...
Me, too.
Wait, now that I've got a closer look, did Yamada style his hair a little differently than usual?
Smooth as ice.
Now I can't remember.
What does it normally look like?
Come to think of it, I never look Yamada in the eye or even at his face when we talk.
Going to a place I've never been.
Wearing something besides my uniform.
Walking together, just us two.
It's hard to believe that we're even part of each other's worlds.
Of all the girls out there, how am I the one walking next to him?
Wanna eat something?
I am kind of peckery.
Wait, I mean hungry.
You know, I'm kind of peckery myself.
I was gonna say peckish and switch words halfway through.
That's normal, right?
Whoa, looks good.
I should've asked this earlier, but is it cool with you that I chose the restaurant?
Mm-hmm.
I've got no idea why, but I was like mega craving a warm meat bun.
Yeah, the weather did cool down.
It did.
It's nice.
I usually stop by Tida's work whenever I want to get some steamies.
But then I caught a whiff of some delicious-smelling meat buns on my way home the other day,
and I thought, I gotta chow down in Chinatown.
Oh, there's this new convenience store I go to.
That's where my boy Tida works.
Tida, the boy with brown hair.
It was hilarious.
Mini had Morimo dying of laughter.
I'm learning more and more names thanks to Yamada's stories.
So I went to ask Apacho if he wanted to go, and uh...
Oh god, have I been talking this whole time?
Here you go.
Uh...
Back in the line?
You lost me.
What?
You used a strange word.
I didn't know what you were talking about when you said steamies.
It's what I call store-bought meat and pizza buns.
I see.
What else were you lost on?
You said you caught a whiff of meat buns.
Curry would make sense, but meat buns don't have a strong smell.
Oh, come on!
They totally do!
You know when the train, when someone's got a takeout box full of them?
It invades your brain.
It's like steak psyops!
Chow down in Chinatown.
Whoa, talk about a delayed reaction.
I can't even remember why I made that joke.
How come you didn't laugh when I said it?
I'm sorry.
It was funny, but you were talking, and I didn't want to interrupt your story.
Interrupt away, girl.
Don't remind me I made a cringe joke way after the fact.
It's like steak psyops.
Now what did I just tell you?
What'd you end up doing on the class trip in your free time?
Um, well, I went to a comedy show.
And I took a lot of scenic photos.
And saw the electronics district.
Sick.
Most of my class just went to Ultra Super Jumbo Land.
The photo you sent me of you guys in the puppy hat was so funny.
Yeah, but now I can't wear it anymore.
Can't recycle the fit.
It's too iconic.
Just this morning, I was nervous about meeting outside of school.
But my anxiety's fading away.
Spending the day with him, around nobody else that I know?
It's weirdly comfortable.
It'd be nice if he felt the same way.
Hey!
Come on, let's walk over to that bridge.
Whoa, check it.
This place is so sick.
It makes the view extra pretty.
What do I do?
It's too much.
I think my heart's going to explode.
I can't look at his face.
Ooh.
Man, that's chilly.
The ocean breeze really hit ya.
Yenbara's still acting normal.
Am I the only one who feels so giddy inside?
Like my emotions are going crazy.
Huh?
Over there.
The boy!
Yenbara!
So fast!
Wait!
Vishi!
The boy!
So fast!
Wait!
Vishi!
You're bad!
So fast!
Wait!
Vishi!
You're bad!
So fast!
Wait!
No, you're bad!
No.
It's so fast!
Wait!
The Dad's over!
You're bad!
No, you're bad!
But you're bad!
No, I'm not really bad!
I'm not really bad!
In fact, all that-
That was close.
Yeesh. I would've preferred a less chaotic ending, but that's life.
Sorry. My curfew's so early.
Hey, don't worry. It's cool.
You? Just focus on breathing.
Oh yeah. When we were making our getaway, you dropped all sorts of stuff.
I don't think I've ever seen you wear these. Do you usually carry them around?
Um, not really?
Well, you should put some of them on.
It'll look cute.
Cute?
I like this fluffy one.
Oh, he means the clip is cute.
Just a sec. This is tough. Girls have mad skills.
Oops. Sorry, it looks weird.
Then again.
Now you can look me in the eye more.
I noticed you don't do very much of that.
Unfortunately, that's not a problem with my bangs.
It's a problem with me.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'll start looking.
Now!
You say that, but your eyes are still closed.
From now on.
Oh, how about now?
Let's hang out again. Just us.
While Yamada and Nishi were about to get their snow on the road, that very same day, about an hour earlier...
earlier. Wow! This rules! A blue sky, a fresh ocean air, and a poppin' place for sightseeing.
Is it just me or is this like an extra dating date? What do I do? My heart's already pounding
like crazy! On the class trip, we had a couple of romantic moments, but most of the time we
were busy hanging with slash near the rest of the crew.
Oh! This is my chance to indulge and get soup snuggly! He won't mind, right? I know
I won't!
Let it hurt!
Because today is special!
Hey, that looks delish!
We're a ways away from where we live. We're alone! I'm gonna need like ten of those. Pick your
poison, Usuke. I gotta enjoy this vacay from everyday life!
Peak choice! I think I'm gonna get a...
Where?
Great! Should we go inside then?
Let's go.
Uh, is...
Hush! Don't speak, don't turn around. No sudden moves. Stay low, stay frosty.
Frosty? What?
Step inside if you know what's good for you.
What's going on?
That's normal, eh?
Why?
Why did he have to show up and burst my lovey-dovey vacay bubble?
Wait a minute! Are those two an official item?
Or are they floating in situationship limbo?
Either way, if they're on a date, things must be going pretty well so far, eh?
Smooth moves, Yamada.
You got this, bud! I'm gonna explode when they make the big announcement.
Yeah! Don't you just love a clear, sunny day?
Yeah.
Yo! Can you dig it?
Uh, dig it?
Cause it's underground, get it?
I guess so.
Yahoo! Yeah!
You know, date night next to the bay has a major grown-up sort of aura.
Like we're super mature adults.
Admitting it makes us sound like kids.
It really does, though.
I like to think I've grown up a little bit.
Yeah, but it's low-key embarrassing when a date is pulled straight out of a chick flick.
I wonder if Yamada and Nish will make it out here later.
If he whisked her away to a fancy spot like this, she'd melt into his arms and be over the moon!
OMG, they could totally be on their way now!
Eh, probably not.
Beautiful.
Huh?
The view.
Oh! Ah! Yeah.
If you want, Mio, we could go over there for a little while.
Really?
Wow! This is pink existence!
Nice skyline.
I've always quietly hoped I'd get to ride a Ferris wheel with someone who's extra special to me!
Quietly?
Loudly, very loudly.
Of course, of course.
When they turn girly romance novels into movies, there's always a cute Ferris wheel scene.
Are they in the books, too?
I wouldn't know.
Just me and the person I love riding a Ferris wheel alone together.
Can I sit over by you?
Huh?
A moment straight from my bucket list!
They are staring right at us.
They really ought to tint these windows.
Selfie time!
What a fun-filled day!
T.B.H., I wish things got a bit mushier, but I didn't want to alert the PDA police.
All the cool lights got me so hyped!
Christmas came early for us!
It really did.
Speaking of Christmas, the best thing about it is all the cozy festive vibes leading up to the actual holiday!
The most wonderful time of the year!
Dingle bells, dingle bells!
Mm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm!
For this Christmas, do you have any plans in mind yet?
Wah!
I'm not sure.
I would be fine with anything if it's with you.
What about you, Yusuke?
Same here.
It's so quiet.
About time.
We finally got a little bit of privacy.
Oh, look who it is!
Hi, Yusuke!
Dad!
No! We were so close!
When you said you wouldn't need dinner, Dad and I took advantage and went on a little date of our own.
Hey, Yusuke. Your house is just over here, right?
Yes, sir. Thank you for the ride.
Wow, you two rode the Ferris wheel.
The view was absolutely gorgeous!
High-speed, unhinged Ferris wheel would be a totally killer ride!
Smell the tea, Suze. What happened?
Well, not to brag, but your girls live in the rom-com dream with extra rum.
Aw, that pin looks cute on you.
Yeah? Thank you, Hone.
So, did you and Yamada have a good time?
What? You went to Chinatown?
That's rad.
Yeah. Convenience store steamies can't compare.
Huh. Yamada went to Chinatown, too.
Who did he go with?
No. Stay nonchalant. Don't engage.
Ooh. It's already starting to get dark out so early.
Hmm. You got ice cube, fingies.
Yours are hot. How are you so warm, Mew?
Yusuke! Yusuke! Look at you!
They added the warm and cozy winter drinks to the vending machine!
Huzzah! When the vending machines say the seasons are changing, then it's real.
You look forward to this every year?
Oh, you can snowbank on it!
You gotta shake them vigorously like a chemistry project for your mouth! You don't want to fail!
Looks intense.
Just like I cherish the changing of the seasons, I want to cherish the little changes between us, too.
Could you, uh, stick to Mew? I like it when you're more casual with me.
Hm?
So, do you like Mew better?
Uh-huh. When I hear Mew, it means Yusuke's all cute and embarrassed.
Hmm. That's a messed up reason.
Mew.
Hey, he's not as embarrassed as before.
Little by little, things are changing.
I'm doing it.
I'm bringing the poles together.
Wait, you're what?
Uh-huh.
There it is.
Yeah.
Mew.
My favorite phrase is in the inside of the world
What do you think?
I'll show you a voice
I'm saying, okay, okay
here to times
I'm saving you a voice
ёр enough
over this day
sl IR
ok
here
I see
I'm
We'll be right back.